God damn
Yesterday I was analyzing data until 3AM
I went through all the price comparison websites,
all the available opinions,
and like 30 reviews and unboxings on YouTube
And what do I get?
I still don't know which to pick
The first one is cheaper and seems to make sense
But, people said that the lifetime leaves a bit to be desired
On the other hand, the second one has the best reviews,
is a bit faster,
but it's simultaneously...
more expensive
But do I need a faster one at all?
From what I've seen on the graphs,
the speed gain is only an illusion
It might not even be noticeable in my case
So, I'll pick the cheaper one because, well...
it is cheaper.
Or maybe not, I'll pick the more expensive one,
because an SD card has to be high quality
Yeah!
I'm picking the more expensive one
For...
17 PLN
Oooh!
You can buy it in installments?!
But hold on
17 PLN in installments?
Like, damn
maybe I'd even take the installments
The fuck do I actually need the card for?
I have like 10 identical ones
No, no, I definitely have to buy that card
The old ones will definitely break
So, I'm buying
Yeah, let's go!
What?
12 PLN for shipping?
Oh!
I can pick it up for free at the store
in Giżycko
Meh, I'll drive
Or maybe I shouldn't?