Password
What "password"?
I've been coming in here for the past 6 years.
Do you not remember? Do you have dementia?
Password
Johnsass
No
Johnass#
JohnsAss#, with uppercase ass
Faster, goddammit, I'm running out of time
Come in
Where the fuck is the Internet?
Fuck you, there isn't any
(connected, no internet)
What, do you think that I don't know where the reset is?
What's your default password?
Where is it?
Hah, it's on your ass
As always, looks like someone took a shit but with characters
Type in, jarsfilledwithlavatory%HGW
You done?
What?
Does Internet work?
Yes, it does
Alright. Now download the Windows update
NO
Sorry, Kacper
What do you mean? It's fine, I can barely feel it
Yeah, sure. You like that, don't you?
He likes it