This is amazing
Hard to describe
It is as if a billion needles stabbed your body
At first, you don't want it
You want to back out of it
And then you are taken by that amazing feeling
That's better than
Than anything else that happened in my life
I would not replace it with, I don't know
With an intoxicating night with Kim Basinger
The one that played that alien in that one movie with that other guy, who played with that other movie
With Aykroyd
With Ibisz?
With Ibisz
Oh fuck, what nice fractals
Ya
Definitely
That is my passion
Nothing will change that
I think about it all the time
And, heh, I think that's the reason to live
Linuxing
It is an amazing hobby, taken up by more and more people
Thousands of distros, consoles, CLIs, and high speeds
Give a feeling of joy, uniqueness and, primarily, freedom
Linux is the only system that adjusts precisely to the needs of the user
And even allows you to sometimes poke your hands around the kernel
(kernel can mean testicle in Polish)
Supposedly you can do everything on it
Faster, better, and often entirely free of charge
The question is, can you run Office on it?
There is OpenOffice. It's the same thing
It's something else, though
The same
What about AutoCAD?
Go away
And Photoshop?
Assshop
And Adobe Premiere Pro?
Fuck off, ok?
Just asking, I am
Fucking leave
That's how the fuckers talk