Hello?
Good morning, Zdzisław Linux here
I'm calling from VaccinaTion
Sir, I don't want to sell you anything
I just wanted to ask, if you know that you will need to get vaccines every year?
No, I do not
Yeah, you will have to
A kind of a subscription if you will
We call it Vaccination as a Service
My God
Yup
And how does it work?
Well, there are different packages
There are Premium, Standard, Bangladesh and Community Edition packages
What's in the Premium?
Premium is a 6 in 1 vaccine
Pfizer.exe, rabies, tetanus, whooping cough, ingrown nails
And rabies
That's nice. I want one then.
That'll be 8900zł. Do you want an invoice?
But you said you didn't want to sell me anything
Of course I don't want to sell
But maybe you want to buy
Do you maybe have something cheaper?
Only the Bangladesh package is cheaper
It's just saliva with the pathogen and vitamin C pills
There's also the reimbursed by the government Community Edition
What's in the reimbursed one?
A jar with air from the mountains
From the upper parts or the lower?
Lower. Who'd ever go into the upper regions?
So many traffic jams are there
There's only one slow ski lift
300zł for the ticket, massive queues
You can't even ski there, people stand in the mud
I bought a ski tour, but, damn it, I'm not even skiing
You know, I stay at home and call people
Alright, alright, I'll get the Premium for that 9k, thank you
Maybe I'll keep the underwear